Frank Bowden Chilton papers, Inclusive: 1800-1964, undated, Bulk: 1887-1933
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Subject Files, 1834-1964, undated; 2
  - Hood’s Texas Brigade — List of those surrendering at Appomattox, 1865 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Hood’s Texas Brigade — Mascot of Brigade, 1865 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Hood’s Texas Brigade — Poems and Stories, 1862-1870, undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Hood’s Texas Brigade — General, 1865-1913 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Family and Friends, 1894-1949, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Photographic Materials, 1800-1927, undated; 3
  This series contains photographs of family, friends, events, and other topics. Various postcards are also present in the series. This series is in fair condition.
  - Family and Friends, 1893, undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Celebrities and Movies, undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Chautauqua, undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Buildings and Scenes, undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Buildings and Scenes, 1874-1910 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Metal Plate Negatives, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Postcards, Texas, Photographic, 1800-1911, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Postcards, Texas, Artistic, 1906-1927, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Collected Materials, 1866-circa 1968, undated; 4
  This series includes materials collected by Frank Chilton or his immediate family. Most of the materials are print materials kept by the family, but not actively created or preserved by them like the subject files. About a third are Civil War related materials. This series is in fair condition.
  - Advertisements, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - United Confederate Veterans General Orders, 1923 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - “Second Annual Celebration of the Battle of Sabine Pass”, 1912 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - “Autographs of Prominent Men of the Southern Confederacy”, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - “The South’s Battle Abbey”, 1894-1895 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - United Confederate Veterans Financial Report, 1913 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - “The Aegis” Houston High School, 1912 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - “The Aegis” Houston High School, 1912 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - "Views of Houston Texas", undated (Box 17 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Broadsides, 1876-1925, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Baptist Young People’s Union Booklets, 1923 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Baptist Young People’s Union Booklet, 1927 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Baptist Young People’s Union Booklet, 1921 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Christmas With the Washingtons, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - The Home Pharmacist, August 1911 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - “Proceedings of the Immigration Convention of Texas”, 1887 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - “Proceedings of the Southern Interstate Immigration Convention”, 1888 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - “Minutes of Union Baptist Association”, 1905 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - “Erminie,” Sheet Music, Undated (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - “The Returned Battle Flags”, June 1905 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Richards Little Encyclopedia, 1899 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Publications, 1911 (Box 17 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - Publications and Newspapers, 1888-1893 (Box 17 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - “Introduction and Prospectus of Krauss’ Southerner”, 1906 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - United Confederate Veterans General Orders, 1923 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - United Confederate Veterans Burial Records, Oakwoods Cemetery, 1892 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - United Confederate Veterans Financial, 1922-1923 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - United Confederate Veterans Reunion in Richmond, Virginia, 1922 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - United Confederate Veterans Reunion in Dallas, Texas, 1925 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - United Confederate Veterans Constitution, 1925 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - “Types of Successful Men of Texas”, undated (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Stamp Prints, undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - “Highlights of Arabia Temple”, 1950 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Bulletins and Church Materials, circa 1957 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Scottish Rite Pamphlets, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - “The Death of General John H. Morgan”, undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Travel, undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Politics, circa 1959 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Poems, circa 1964 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - “Confederate Veteran”, 1932 December (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - “United Daughters of the Confederacy Magazine”, 1963 October (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - “United Daughters of the Confederacy Magazine”, 1964 May-July (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - “United Daughters of the Confederacy Magazine”, 1964 September-November (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - “United Daughters of the Confederacy Magazine”, 1968 February-April (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - “United Daughters of the Confederacy Magazine”, 1968 May-July (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - “United Daughters of the Confederacy Magazine”, 1968 August-October (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - “United Daughters of the Confederacy Magazine”, 1968 November-December (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - “United Daughters of the Confederacy Magazine”, 1969 January-February (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - “The Old Guard” Magazine, 1866 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - “Frontier Times”, 1924 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - “Cumberland University Magazine”, 1893 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - “Confederate War Journal”, 1893 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - “The Texas Pioneer”, 1937 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Artifacts, 1911, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Hood’s Texas Brigade Association, 1910, undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Hood’s Texas Brigade Association, 1911-1917 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - General, undated (Box 17 OVZ, Folder 4)
- Scrapbooks, 1865-1955, undated; 5
  This series includes many scrapbooks on various topics, including Texas and the South, Civil War, and family poetry and notebooks. The Hood's Texas Brigade scrapbooks contain materials on veterans reunions, letters from veterans, and other information from the war and afterward. This series is in poor condition.
  - General, 1898-1937 (Box 15 OVZ)
  - General, 1935, 1943-1945, 1953 (Box 16 OVZ)
  - General, 1954-1955 (Box 17 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Texas, 1923-1943 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Texas, 1923-1943 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Texas, 1923-1943 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Texas, 1923-1943 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - South, 1869-1935 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - South, 1869-1935 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - South, 1869-1935 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - South, 1869-1935 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Hood’s Texas Brigade, 1865-1933 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Hood’s Texas Brigade, 1865-1933 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Mabel Bowers Notebook, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Mabel Bowers Poetry Book, 1899 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Poetry Book, undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Irene Chilton, 1911 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Artifacts, undated; 6
  This series contains primarily post-Civil War reunion artifacts, including a key to the city that was presented to the veterans, ribbons and stamps, and a letter opener. The stamps are large printing plates that would have been used to create stationery with that specific design stamped into the paper. Some correspondence can be found in the collection that was stamped with the stamps preserved in this collection. This series is in good condition.
  - Alamo letter opener, undated (Box 18 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Flag stamps, undated (Box 18 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Texas and Confederate National Flag stamps, undated (Box 18 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Texas Capital and people stamp, undated (Box 18 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Frank Bowden Chilton stamp (1 of 4), undated (Box 18 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Wooden key, 1908 (Box 19 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Frank Bowden Chilton stamp (2 of 4), undated (Box 20 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Frank Bowden Chilton stamp (3 of 4), undated (Box 20 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Frank Bowden Chilton stamp (4 of 4), undated (Box 20 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Frank Bowden Chilton and Soldiers stamps, undated (Box 20 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Hood's Texas Brigade Monument stamp, undated (Box 21 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Robert E. Lee and Thomas J. "Stonewall" Jackson stamp, undated (Box 21 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Second Confederate National Flag stamp, undated (Box 22 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Robert E. Lee stamp, undated (Box 22 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - John Bell Hood stamp, undated (Box 22 OVZ, Folder 3)